pncvirtualwallet.com 2015-09-06

# PNC Bank - Privacy Policy

**Personal Information**

Personal information refers to any information about you that is personally identifiable to you. Your telephone number, name, address, and transaction history are examples of information that pertain to you personally.

**Data**

Data in the context of our online and mobile privacy policy generally refers to other information that we collect through your internet or mobile activities or which third parties may collect on our behalf. Such data may or may not be personally identifiable to you. Geolocation data collected from your mobile device when you ask for the location of the nearest ATM is personally identifiable when obtained through Mobile Banking.

**Information Collection**  
**We Collect Personal Information About You When:**

  * **You Provide Personal Information to Us --**  
PNC collects personal information online that you provide to us, such as when you log in, on applications you complete, and when you use our products and services. See _What Does PNC Do With Your Personal Information_ for more information about what personal information is collected, how, and why.
  * **We Obtain Personal Information from Others --**  
We obtain personal information from third parties such as credit bureaus and others to tailor your online experience.
  * **We Gather Information Online --**  
PNC uses tools, such as cookies or click stream auditing, to gather information for internal uses, such as Web analytics and to personalize your visit.

**Cookies**  
Cookies are small pieces of information that a Web site stores on a visitor's Web browser to remind the site about the visitor the next time they visit the site. PNC does not store confidential or sensitive personal information in cookies. PNC uses cookies to enhance our customers' online banking session by making navigation easier and providing important security features. For certain applications, such as Online Banking, cookies are a requirement because they help protect the privacy of a customer's transactions by, for example, automatically terminating the online session if the customer forgets to log out.

Cookies cannot be used to capture your e-mail address, obtain data from your hard drive or gain confidential or sensitive information about you. Additionally, cookies cannot be read by a Web site other than the one that set the cookie. Some Web sites, however, use cookies to obtain information from your browser. You can set your browser to notify you before accepting a cookie, so that you can control whether you accept or reject a cookie. You will need to manage your cookie settings for each device and browser you use. Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preference.

**Click stream auditing**

Click Stream Auditing includes information such as a web surfer's IP address, web pages which have been viewed or acted upon by a web surfer, date and time, domain type, and when a web surfer has responded to an advertisement. We may occasionally combine this information with individual information on an aggregate level to determine the effectiveness of our advertising.

**Action Tags and Other Technologies**

Action Tags are commonly referred to as Web beacons or GIF tags. This type of technology is inserted in various places within our Web site to collect anonymous information about your visits to the PNC site and your interaction with our ads and content. PNC may use certain technologies to collect additional information related to the status and condition of your mobile devices.  This information may be used to support the security of your transaction with PNC, determine industry trends, and for other research purposes.

**Information Use**

Personal information that we collect about you is used to provide you with optimal online experiences with us. We use it to help determine your financial interests and needs in order to recommend relevant products and services. We use personal information about you to qualify you for products and services that you request, to process your transactions, authenticate your identity, prevent fraud, and to keep your information and financial transactions secure.

**Information Sharing**

PNC shares your personal information within its family of PNC companies (affiliates) and with select third parties in accordance with the terms described in our privacy notice, _What Does PNC Do With Your Personal Information_. The notice also provides a toll free number for you to limit certain sharing. Additional information is provided below under **Advertising and Tracking** and under **Your Options**. We may share personal information when required by law or a subpoena or court order. We may also share personal information when we suspect fraud or for risk management purposes.

**Children**

PNC websites and mobile applications are not directed to children and do not knowingly collect information from children.

**Access**

PNC does not maintain a process which allows visitors to review and request changes to any of his or her personally identifiable information, including information that is collected through the use of cookies or other tracking devices, on the Web site or our online service. If you believe that PNC customer records contain any incorrect information about you, please contact us using the customer service contact information provided on your bank or investment statements, or other communications from us pertaining to the products and services you use. You may also contact your local branch, relationship manager, or broker.

**Retention and Destruction**

PNC retains personally identifiable information as long as necessary to provide the products and services for which the information was collected, to process and maintain a record of transactions, and as long as necessary for legal process or to satisfy government retention requirements. When the retention period expires, PNC destroys data that was maintained in any form in a manner that renders it completely unusable and incapable of restoration.
